okay so we got a couple problems here
I just got back from came out and
taking a dump in the back
and when you will leave in the store get
this I hope you bottomed on some DVD are
you kidding me you think you can just
buy bonds on DVD lock it your own
business no you don't look like that you
know what I got up in this town
we all saw gonna Brown fans here and I
saw you run home
I saw you lock the door for your window
and I gotta kill you actually I
am gonna kill you and I'm gonna take
your wallet to go buy some socks on DVDs
because I talked to the police
they said yeah he's a mile off man go
kill him Tammuz be his ass
so I thought okay I will
[Music]
damn you lock the door
fine I'll climb up the window instead
[Music]
what the is this you locked the
window too you you think
that I'll stop me me I'm telling the
fire you know what I gotta be
honest well I was like talking to you
and that was all part of my plan I
tricked you
you know why cuz while we were
talking Uncle Chuck was sneaking around
back lock unlocking lock that you the
back doing he's coming in right
this instant he is gonna rape
your ass and kill you
[Music]
go outside
Uncle Chuck you probably all kills you
hi
[Music]
you auntie thought you could go away
washing them on sock beauty that's funny
here's a sock on DVD for you
what's that instead before you die